<resources>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="high">High</string>
    <string name="low">Low</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="up_down_value">Change</string>
    <string name="up_down_rate">Change%</string>
    <string name="volume">Amount</string>

    <string name="min_time">Line</string>
    <string name="min_1">1min</string>
    <string name="min_5">5min</string>
    <string name="min_15">15min</string>
    <string name="min_30">30min</string>
    <string name="hour_1">1hour</string>
    <string name="hour_6">6hour</string>
    <string name="day_1">1day</string>
    <string name="week_1">1week</string>
    <string name="month_1">1month</string>
    <string name="more">More</string>

    <string name="main_view">Main</string>
    <string name="second_view">Sec</string>
    <string name="target_setting">Index settings</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="introduction">Introduction</string>
    <string name="introduction_ma">The MA indicator is connected by the average of the closing prices over a period of time, which can smooth the short-term fluctuations and reflect the long-term trend or cycle.</string>
    <string name="introduction_boll">The BOLL indicator is also called the Bollinger Band. Its basic form is a band-shaped channel composed of three orbit lines (one for each of the middle and upper and lower rails). The middle rail is the average cost of the price, and the upper rail and the lower rail can be regarded as the pressure line and support line of the price, respectively.</string>
    <string name="introduction_macd">The MACD indicator consists of a set of curves and graphics. It is calculated by the difference between the fast or slow change of the price or index at the close and the slow-moving exponential moving average (EMA). Short-term EMA, and "L" refers to longer-term EMA, the most commonly used are 12-day and 26-day EMA</string>
    <string name="introduction_kdj">The KDJ indicator passes the highest price, the lowest price, and the closing price of the last calculation cycle in a specific cycle (usually 9 days, 9 weeks, etc.) and between these three. To calculate the immature random value of the last calculation period, and then calculate the K value, D value and J value according to the method of smoothing moving average, and draw a graph to study the price trend</string>
    <string name="introduction_rsi">The RS indicator is a technical analysis tool that compares price movements to express price intensity. Among them, the 14-day RS is the most representative.</string>
    <string name="introduction_wr">The WR indicator is an oscillating indicator, which measures whether it is overbought or oversold according to the price swing point. It measures the ratio of the distance between the peak (highest price) created by the long and short sides to the daily closing price and the price fluctuation range within a certain period of time (such as days, 14 days, 28 days, etc.) to provide a signal of price trend reversal .</string>
</resources>
